The road less traveled is about to get some company.
Moving McAllister is a comedy, romance film directed by Andrew Black.
Rick Robinson, a law intern, is scheduled to take
the bar exam in just four days.
Anxious to score points with his boss Mr.
McAllister, Rick unwisely agrees to help the man move.
The next day, Rick finds himself in a moving van from Miami to Los Angeles,
accompanied by McAllister's spoiled niece and her pet pig.
Rick Robinson, played by Ben Gourley.
Michelle McAllister, played by Mila Kunis.
Orlie, played by Jon Heder.
Maxwell McAllister, played by Rutger Hauer.
Carl, played by Hubbel Palmer.
The Lady, played by Billy Drago.
Moving McAllister is a 2007 American comedy film starring Ben Gourley,
Mila Kunis, Jon Heder, Rutger Hauer, and Billy Drago.
The film was shot largely in Utah and St Johns County,
Florida and was produced by Camera 40 Productions.
It was released on September 14, 2007, in the United States.
The film explores themes of pig, road trip, hitchhiker, intern.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.